thompsonpump.com 2013-04-20

# Dewatering Pumps | Rental Pumps - Thompson Pump - Privacy Policy

Home : Privacy Policy

Thompson Pump & Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Thompson) is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this Web site.

Information Collected  
In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. In addition, there are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address. For electronic access to annual reports and proxy statements, we collect your tax identification number to verify your shareholder status. For our supplier diversity site, we necessarily collect information about gender and ethnicity, such as whether your business is female-owned. This Web site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children. 

Use of Collected Information  
Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site. 

When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information. Usually, we use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your request (such as to receive annual reports or sales information). This information may be shared with other Thompson businesses, but only if necessary to fulfill your request or for related purposes. 

Links to Other Sites  
Thompson's Web site may contain links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites. 

Security of Collected Information  
We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those Thompson workers who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Workers who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action. 

Access to Collected Information  
You may review and update the information that you provide to us through this Web site by contacting us as described below. 

Contacting Us  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy. 

Changes to this Policy  
Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any change. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this Web site of any major changes for at least 30 days following the change.
